<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.hello.bigclean.scanner</id>
    <name>BigClean Scanner</name>
    <vendor>Hello Sheng</vendor>
    <version>1.0.0</version>
    
    <!-- Proprietary License Declaration -->
    <license>Proprietary</license>
    <icon>icons/pluginIcon.svg</icon>
    <icon dark="true">icons/pluginIcon_dark.svg</icon>

    <description><![CDATA[
    <h2>BigClean Scanner - Code Cleanup Analysis Tool</h2>
    
    <p>A powerful IntelliJ IDEA plugin for analyzing unused code in your projects, helping developers clean and maintain their codebase. This tool provides comprehensive analysis capabilities to identify and remove dead code, improving code quality and maintainability.</p>
    
    <h3>Key Features:</h3>
    <ul>
        <li><b>Unused Class Analysis</b> - Uses two different analysis methods to identify unused classes</li>
        <li><b>Regex Analysis</b> - Fast scanning, suitable for preliminary analysis</li>
        <li><b>Spoon AST Analysis</b> - Precise syntax analysis providing more accurate results</li>
        <li><b>Unused Method Analysis</b> - Identifies methods that are not called in the project</li>
        <li><b>Independent Refresh</b> - Each analysis module can be refreshed independently</li>
        <li><b>Spring Framework Support</b> - Optimized analysis specifically for Spring projects</li>
    </ul>
    
    <h3>How to Use:</h3>
    <ol>
        <li>Find "BigClean Scanner" in the right tool window</li>
        <li>Select the project to analyze</li>
        <li>Click the corresponding refresh button to start analysis</li>
        <li>Review analysis results and clean up unused code</li>
    </ol>
    
    <h3>Supported Analysis Types:</h3>
    <ul>
        <li>Spring @Component, @Service, @Repository, @Controller</li>
        <li>AspectJ @Aspect annotations</li>
        <li>MapStruct @Mapper annotations</li>
        <li>Lombok annotation classes</li>
        <li>JUnit test classes</li>
        <li>Configuration property classes</li>
    </ul>
    
    <p><em>Note: Analysis results are for reference only. Please verify carefully before actually deleting code.</em></p>
    
    <h3>License:</h3>
    <p>This plugin is proprietary software. All rights reserved. Redistribution and use in source and binary forms, with or without modification, are not permitted without explicit written permission from the author.</p>
    ]]></description>

    <!-- please see https://www.jetbrains.org/intellij/sdk/docs/basics/getting_started/plugin_compatibility.html
         on how to target different products -->
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.java</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <!-- Add your extensions here -->
        <toolWindow id="BigClean Scanner"
                    anchor="right"
                    icon="icons/pluginIcon.svg"
                    factoryClass="com.hello.bigclean.ClassPathAnalyzerFactory"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
    </actions>
</idea-plugin>